[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What would you describe the mood tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well tonight, Piers, things have really come down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Hi, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "How are you doing tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "There's a huge disconnect, isn't there now, between the two?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What has gone fundamentally wrong with America to cause what is going on now at Wall Street and other cities?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, the fact that the Democrats and Republicans, and both of them are equally guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Who don't you like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, there's only one person that I like at all of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Can you imagine the money we could put forward to our infrastructure if we weren't involved in these two stupid wars that we've been in for 10 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I mean, Ron Paul is unlikely the way the polls are looking to win.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "What do you think of the rest of the field?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Well, Newt Gingrich, it's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Would you agree if the CIA discovered tomorrow that they knew where Osama bin Laden was that he should be assassinated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "What about Gadhafi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "You don't care?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 147, "question": "We just go out, and if people we don't like, we kill them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Isn't that --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Everyone is willing to be killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Jesse, with respect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Isn't that exactly what Navy SEALs do all the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "No, when in war.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "How do I know they're telling me the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Well, let me ask you a direct question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Do you believe bin Laden is dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Laden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":"], "qSentId": 211, "question": "How do we know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "What was your view of Gadhafi being taken out in public in the way that he was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "What troubled me about it was our media here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Have you decided yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I will vote absolutely for Ron Paul if he -- if he runs as an independent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Would you feel comfortable discussing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, let's talk about your wealth first.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$25 million"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "stroke NBC $24 million?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, it's actually $25 million.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$24 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "You're the queen of television, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I'm not the queen of television.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "And you've parted company with Andre, your boyfriend of some time, this year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andre"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I can't speak about that publicly out of a personal request.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Why leave him out of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Because, you know, I just -- I made a promise to someone, so I like to be a man of my word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "But it was your decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I don't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "You don't remember?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "You can't remember whose decision it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "It was almost three weeks ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Are you enjoying being single again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I'm happy to -- I mean I'm just happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Are you on the prowl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What do you like about them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I like -- I don't know, I like to be challenged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "What do you think of the Demi-Ashton split today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I just heard of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Well, you just told me about it backstage, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 360, "question": "You think so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Well, yes, I think they probably had a lot of good times with some other women and then --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "How do you know this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Well, come on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What lines?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "The lines of cocaine on the table.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Let's -- yes, lets show some little clip of what they said about the marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "And they seemed -- I mean, to me, they seemed very much in love at the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Do you tolerate infidelity yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "How is he doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "ORGAN: Good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "What was the closest you came?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "I've never come close to marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Because I know you kind of fancy yourself on politics, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Is he right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "The chances are you probably will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "We are just very competitive over everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "ANDLER: Oh, because all of all your reality world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "The political landscape?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Well, where shall we start?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Let's start with Republicans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What do we make of Herman Cain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Well, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "He's engaging, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Well, I think the whole point now in politics is to kind of get yourself out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain", "Michele Bachmann", "Ron Paul"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "I think that's what he's up to, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "But no, no, I firmly believe that people like Herman Cain and Michele Bachmann, and -- I think that they all really -- I mean Ron Paul, probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Did you see the video of him when they asked about Libya and Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "He didn't seem to know what Libya was.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "ORGAN: Why don't you go into politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Well, let me tell you why.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Are you British?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I am a Brit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "I beg your pardon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "No, you don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "You are, I think the word is flushing, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "I'm flushing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Yes, flushing and blushing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "He was just much older.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "You want to pay more tax?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "The government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "Where are you supposed to write the check to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Do you not watch any news?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "Wouldn't that be cool?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Well, It wouldn't make any sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Because you were staying in the break how, under different circumstances, you'd go for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "Well, that's one version of what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "No, when did that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "They got him back for the third year, despite all the anger last year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "Is Hollywood beginning to understand that kind of humor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 812, "question": "Wasn't it two years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 813, "answer": "Yes, but I think it's been getting worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "It's about stop taking yourself too seriously, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "Well, I believe it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "RBR", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "Is that what we're worried about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "I hope there are more cutaways to all their faces when he -- when I had Ricky on the show just after the Globes last year, it was brilliant, because when I played back the stuff to him, he never laughed at the punch line.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "Historic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "It can be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 842, "question": "About who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 843, "answer": "Anyone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "50 Cent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "Why are you repeating what I said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "Because I'm speaking now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "Are you a listener?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "Keep the shameless plugs down to a minimum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 888, "question": "Don't you have a baby on the way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 889, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "Wouldn't you plug that baby, if you could?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "No, I wouldn't, because I protect my own privacy unlike you American celebrities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "How do you want this interview to be remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "First of all, you have a new show every day, just like I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "Oh, this is like Nixon/Frost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "It's a bit like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 920, "question": "Because everyone is just banging on about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 921, "answer": "You have a chubby face.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "111117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 924, "question": "What would you call it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 925, "answer": "Well rounded, well fed, we would say in England.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]